It's fine
Not worth it
Did you really marry Fu Chenzhou
Yeah
How could you be so impulsive
How long have you even known him
I've known Gu Chengze
for so long but still couldn't see through him
Time spent doesn't mean they're worth it
I'm not going home tonight
I'll go back and clear things up tomorrow
Tonight I don't want to
go back to that wedding
It's fake
She's just putting on a show for me
But someone took a picture of them
coming out of the Civil Affairs Bureau
Brother Chengze
Did Sister really get married
Is Sister still mad at me
When will you sign the authorization
Are we really talking about this now
Tonight is already a mess
The Gu family needs to reassure the partners
I got it
She'll come back begging me
Have someone keep an eye on her
And Fu Chenzhou too
Understood
Brother Chengze
Is Fu Chenzhou really just a bodyguard